pluspremieres.nz 2019-04-28

# Privacy Policy | Plus Premieres

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Plus Premieres collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of [Plus Premieres](https://pluspremieres.us/). This privacy policy applies to the site and all products and services offered by Plus Premieres.

Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain site related activities.

Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Web browser cookies

Our site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the site may not function properly.

How we use collected information

Plus Premieres may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

\- To improve our site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
\- To run a promotion, contest, survey or other site feature  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.  
\- To send periodic emails  
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our site.

Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licencors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you.

Google Ads

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. Google will collect additional data for Display and Search Remarketing ([Click here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2611268?hl=en&utm_id=ad) for more info).

Google Analytics

Plus Premieres uses Google Analytics to collect data about our traffic. Plus Premieres will use this data to better serve it's traffic and to better understand it's traffic flow and pages of interest. Google will collect additional data for Display and Search Remarketing ([Click here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2611268?hl=en&utm_id=ad) for more info). If you'd like to prevent your data from being used by Google you may opt out [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

Changes to this privacy policy

Plus Premieres has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your acceptance of these terms

We notify the User of this agreement upon first visit to this site. The User will be notified with any changes in these terms upon next visit. Your continued use of the site will be deemed your acceptance of these terms.

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or any other matters, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#bcdfd3d2c8dddfc8fcccd0c9cfccced9d1d5d9ced9cf92c9cf) or by submitting a message on our [contact page](https://pluspremieres.us/p/contact.html). Please see our DMCA page for

This document was last updated on May 30th, 2019
